{
	"quiz": "Quiz 1",
	"quizId": "quiz1",
	"questions": [{
		"question": "/Sqrt(4)^3",
		"answers": ["8", "16", "6", "12", "dog"]
	}, {
		"question": "When measuring the amount of medicine to administer, you should use:",
		"answers": ["Teaspoon", "Millilleter", "Gram"]
	}, {
		"question": "What is the solution set for 'x^2+4x+5=0'?",
		"answers": ["No Solution", "[-2+i,-2-i]", "[2,-2]"]
    }, {
		"question": "[image]",
		"answers": ["True", "False", "I don't know"]
	}, {
		"question": "Which of the following is equivilant to (x^2-4)^2",
		"answers": ["(x-2)^4", "(x-2)^2*(x+2)^2", "(x+4)^3(x-1)"]
	}, {
		"question": "Rewrite the following equation: (x-3)(x+2)(x-1)",
		"answers": ["x^3+8x^2+8x+8", "3x^3-2x^2+5x+8", "x^3-2x^2-4x+8"]
	}, {
		"question": "What is the point of intersect between y=-3x and y=x^2+2",
		"answers": ["(0,0)", "(-1,3)", "(2,6)"]
	}, {
		"question": "[image]",
		"answers": ["2", "4", "1"]
	}, {
		"question": "Students are modelling the St. Louis Arc. If the center of the arc is placed on the y axis. (0,630). Where does it cross the x-aixs?",
		"answers": ["(315,0),(-315,0)", "(0,315)(0,-315)", "(125,0),(-275,0)"]
	}, {
		"question": "When rolling a pair of dice and flipping a coin, What is more likely to occur: 1)Rolling a 7 or 11 and a head or 2( rolling a sum of 13 and tails",
		"answers": ["1", "2", "They are equal"]
	}]
}